Guide to the Sports Memorabilia Collection SC0814
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Sports Memorabilia, Accession ARCH-2008-018
  - Miscellaneous Items:
    - 2005 Deck of playing cards depicting Southern California Olympic Swimmers (Box 11)
    - 9 USA Olympic Pins from the 2000 Olympics in Sydney, Aust. (Box 11)
    - 2 SF 49ers season ticket holder pins (Box 11)
    - NBA "Medallion Collection" pin of Pau Gasol - Memphis Grizzlies (Box 11)
    - 2005 Mini Rose Bowl football - limited edition issue (Box 11)
    - 2007 SF 49ers Season ticket holder handbook (Box 11)
  - Sports Illustrated magazines, 8/13/07 - 12/10/07 (Box 11)
  - Sports Illustrated magazines, 10/23/2000, 1/9/06 - 10/16/06 (Box 12)
  - Sports Illustrated magazines, 10/23/06 - 8/6/07 (Box 13)
- Sports Memorabilia, Accession ARCH-2008-104
  - PRO! The official publication of the National Football League
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Dallas Cowboys, "Rookie Game," July 21, 1969 (Box 1)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. New Orleans Saints, August 8, 1969 (5 copies) (Box 1)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. Oakland Raiders, August 16, 1969 (3 copies) (Box 1)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. Cleveland Browns, August 23, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. New York Jets, August 25, 1696 (Box 1)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. Los Angeles Rams, August 30, 1696 (4 copies) (Box 1)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. St. Louis Cardinals, September 7, 1969 (Box 1)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. Kansas City Chiefs, September 14, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Miami Dolphins, September 20, 1969 (Box 1)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. New York Jets, September 28, 1969 (Box 1)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. Cincinnati Bengals, October 4, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Buffalo Bills, October 19, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Denver Broncos, November 9, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. San Diego Chargers, November 16, 1969 (Box 1)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. Denver Broncos, November 23, 1969 (3 copies) (Box 1)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. Boston Patriots, December 7, 1969 (Box 1)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. Dallas Cowboys, August 8, 1970 (5 copies) (Box 1)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Baltimore Colts, August 8, 1970 (2 copies) (Box 1)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. New York Giants, August 15, 1970 (3 copies) (Box 1)
    - Los Angeles Rams vs. Oakland Raiders, August 22, 1970 (Box 1)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. Chicago Bears, August 24, 1970 (Box 1)
    - Pittsburgh Steelers vs. New York Giants, "Football Dedication – Three Rivers Stadium," August 28, 1970 (Box 1)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. Los Angeles Rams, August 29, 1970 (Box 1)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Green Bay Packers, August 30, 1970 (Box 1)
    - Green Bay Packers vs. Cincinnati Bengals, September 5, 1970 (Box 1)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Oakland Raiders, September 6, 1970 (2 copies) (Box 1)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Pittsburgh Steelers, September 12, 1970 (Box 1)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. Baltimore Colts, September 20, 1970 (2 copies) (Box 1)
    - San Diego Charger vs. Oakland Raiders, September 27, 1970 (2 copies) (Box 1)
    - Los Angeles Rams vs. San Diego Chargers, October 4, 1970 (Box 1)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Denver Broncos, October 11, 1970 (Box 1)
  - PRO! The official publication of the National Football League, cont.
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Washington Redskins, October 19, 1970 (Box 2)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. Houston Oilers, October 25, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Pittsburgh Steelers, October 25, 1970 (Box 2)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Green Bay Packers, November 1, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Los Angeles Rams vs. Atlanta Falcons, November 8, 1970 (Box 2)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. Denver Broncos, November 8, 1970 (2 copies) (Box 2)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Cleveland Browns, November 8, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Los Angeles Rams vs. New York Jets, November 15, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. San Diego Chargers, November 22, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Los Angeles Rams vs. New Orleans Saints, December 6, 1970 (Box 2)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. Cincinnati Bengals, December 6, 1970 (2 copies) (Box 2)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Kansas City Chiefs, December 12, 1970 (3 copies) (Box 2)
    - Los Angeles Rams vs. Detroit Lions, December 14, 1970 (Box 2)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. Kansas City Chiefs, December 20, 1970 (2 copies) (Box 2)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. San Francisco 49ers, December 20, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Philadelphia Eagles, August 9, 1971 (3 copies) (Box 2)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Los Angeles Rams, August 21, 1971 (Box 2)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. Atlanta Falcons, September 11, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Philadelphia Eagles, October 17, 1971 (2 copies) (Box 2)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Kansas City Chiefs, October 31, 1971 (Box 2)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Kansas City Chiefs, December 6, 1971 (2 copies) (Box 2)
    - Los Angeles Rams vs. Washington Redskins, December 13, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. New England Patriots, August 5, 1972 (Box 2)
    - New York Jets vs. Pittsburgh Steelers, August 12, 1972 (Box 2)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Cleveland Browns, August 13, 1972 (Box 2)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Baltimore Colts, August 14, 1972 (Box 2)
    - Los Angeles Rams vs. Oakland Raiders, August 19, 1972 (Box 2)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Buffalo Bills, August 26, 1972 (Box 2)
  - PRO! The official publication of the National Football League, cont.
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Oakland Raiders, September 3, 1972 (Box 3)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. San Diego Chargers, September 17, 1972 (Box 3)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. San Diego Chargers, October 1, 1972 (Box 3)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Buffalo Bills, October 15, 1972 (Box 3)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. New York Giants, October 15, 1972 (2 copies) (Box 3)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. New Orleans Saints, October 22, 1972 (Box 3)
    - Los Angeles Rams vs. Cincinnati Bengals, October 22, 1972 (Box 3)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Los Angeles Rams, October 29, 1972 (Box 3)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. Kansas City Chiefs, October 29, 1972 (Box 3)
    - Los Angeles Rams vs. Atlanta Falcons, November 5, 1972 (Box 3)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Baltimore Colts, November 12, 1972 (2 copies) (Box 3)
    - Los Angeles Rams vs. Minnesota Vikings, November 19, 1972 (Box 3)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Kansas City Chiefs, November 26, 1972 (Box 3)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Los Angeles Rams, December 4, 1972 (Box 3)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. New York Jets, December 11, 1972 (Box 3)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Minnesota Vikings, December 16, 1972 (2 copies) (Box 3)
    - Los Angeles Rams vs. Detroit Lions, December 17, 1972 (Box 3)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Dallas Cowboys, August 11, 1973 (Box 3)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Miami Dolphins, September 23, 1973 (3 copies) (Box 3)
    - Los Angeles Rams vs. Dallas Cowboys, October 14, 1973 (Box 3)
    - Los Angeles Rams vs. Green Bay Packers, October 21, 1973 (Box 3)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Atlanta Falcons, October 28, 1973 (2 copies) (Box 3)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Pittsburgh Steelers, November 11, 1973 (Box 3)
  - PRO! The official publication of the National Football League, cont.
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Cleveland Browns, November 18, 1973 (Box 4)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Philadelphia Eagles, December 2, 1973 (Box 4)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Kansas City Chiefs, December 8, 1973 (2 copies) (Box 4)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Denver Broncos, December 16, 1973 (2 copies) (Box 4)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Denver Broncos, August 18, 1974 (Box 4)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Philadelphia Eagles, August 24, 1974 (Box 4)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Oakland Raiders, September 2, 1974 (2 copies) (Box 4)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Los Angeles Rams, September 8, 1974 (Box 4)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Kansas City Chiefs, September 22, 1974 (2 copies) (Box 4)
    - Cincinnati Bengals vs. San Francisco 49ers, September 29, 1974 (Box 4)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Cincinnati Bengals, October 20, 1974 (Box 4)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. San Francisco 49ers, October 27, 1974 (Box 4)
    - Los Angeles Rams vs. San Francisco 49ers, November 4, 1974 (Box 4)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. San Diego Chargers, November 17, 1974 (Box 4)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Atlanta Falcons, November 24, 1974 (Box 4)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Detroit Lions, August 10, 1975 (Box 4)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. San Francisco 49ers, August 30, 1975 (Box 4)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Los Angeles Rams, September 28, 1975 (2 copies) (Box 4)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Atlanta Falcons, October 12, 1975 (Box 4)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Atlanta Falcons, November 30, 1975 (Box 4)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. Kansas City Chiefs, December 21, 1975 (Box 4)
    - Pittsburgh Steelers vs. Oakland Raiders, September 12, 1976 (2 copies) (Box 4)
    - Washington Redskins vs. San Francisco 49ers, November 7, 1976 (Box 4)
    - Los Angeles Rams vs. San Francisco 49ers, November 21, 1976 (Box 4)
    - Minnesota Vikings vs. San Francisco 49ers, November 29, 1976 (Box 4)
    - Cincinnati Bengals vs. Oakland Raiders, December 6, 1976 (Box 4)
    - Seattle Seahawks vs. San Francisco 49ers, August 7, 1977 (Box 4)
    - Los Angeles Rams vs. San Francisco 49ers, August 21, 1977 (Box 4)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Oakland Raiders, September 3, 1977 (Box 4)
  - PRO! The official publication of the National Football League, cont.
    - Denver Broncos vs. San Francisco 49ers, September 10, 1977 (3 copies) (Box 5)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Miami Dolphins, September 25, 1977 (Box 5)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Atlanta Falcons, October 9, 1977 (Box 5)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Detroit Lions, October 23, 1977 (Box 5)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Tampa Bay Buccaneers, October 30, 1977 (Box 5)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Los Angeles Rams, November 20, 1977 (4 copies) (Box 5)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. New Orleans Saints, November 27, 1977 (Box 5)
    - Dallas Cowboys vs. San Francisco 49ers, December 12, 1977 (2 copies) (Box 5)
    - Chicago Bears vs. San Francisco 49ers, September 10, 1978 (4 copies) (Box 5)
    - Cincinnati Bengals vs. San Francisco 49ers, October 1, 1978 (Box 5)
    - New Orleans Saints vs. San Francisco 49ers, October 15, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Atlanta Falcons vs. San Francisco 49ers, October 22, 1978 (Box 5)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. Oakland Raiders, October 29, 1978 (Box 5)
    - St. Louis Cardinals vs. San Francisco 49ers, November 12, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Los Angeles Rams vs. San Francisco 49ers, November 19, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Pittsburgh Steelers vs. San Francisco 49ers, November 27, 1978 (3 copies) (Box 5)
    - Denver Broncos vs. Oakland Raiders, December 3, 1978 (2 copies) (Box 5)
    - Tampa Bay Buccaneers vs. San Francisco 49ers, December 10, 1978 (3 copies) (Box 5)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. San Francisco 49ers, August 4, 1979 (2 copies) (Box 5)
    - Denver Broncos vs. San Francisco 49ers, August 18, 1979 (Box 5)
    - Dallas Cowboys vs. San Francisco 49ers, September 9, 1979 (Box 5)
    - New Orleans vs. Saints San Francisco 49ers, September 23, 1979 (Box 5)
    - Seattle Seahawks vs. San Francisco 49ers, October 7, 1979 (3 copies) (Box 5)
    - Los Angeles Rams vs. New Orleans Saints, October 7, 1979 (Box 5)
    - Atlanta Falcons vs. San Francisco 49ers, October 21, 1979 (Box 5)
  - PRO! The official publication of the National Football League, cont.
    - San Diego Chargers vs. Oakland Raiders, October 25, 1979 (3 copies) (Box 6)
    - Chicago Bears vs. San Francisco 49ers, October 28, 1979 (2 copies) (Box 6)
    - Denver Broncos vs. San Francisco 49ers, November 18, 1979 (3 copies) (Box 6)
    - Los Angeles Rams vs. San Francisco 49ers, November 25, 1979 (3 copies) (Box 6)
    - Tampa Bay Buccaneers vs. San Francisco 49ers, December 9, 1979 (2 copies) (Box 6)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. San Francisco 49ers, August 9, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Seattle Seahawks vs. San Francisco 49ers, August 23, 1980 (3 copies) (Box 6)
    - St. Louis Cardinals vs. San Francisco 49ers, September 14, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Atlanta Falcons vs. San Francisco 49ers, September 28, 1980 (Box 6)
    - San Diego Chargers vs. Oakland Raiders, October 12, 1980 (3 copies) (Box 6)
    - Los Angeles Rams vs. San Francisco 49ers, October 19, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Tampa Bay Buccaneers vs. San Francisco 49ers, October 26, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Seattle Seahawks vs. Oakland Raiders, October 26, 1980 (Box 6)
    - New York Giants vs. San Francisco 49ers, November 23, 1980 (Box 6)
  - PRO! The official publication of the National Football League, cont.
    - New England Patriots vs. San Francisco 49ers, November 30, 1980 (Box 7)
    - New Orleans Saints vs. San Francisco 49ers, December 7, 1980 (Box 7)
    - Buffalo Bills vs. San Francisco 49ers, December 21, 1980 (Box 7)
  - GameDay PRO!
    - Seattle Seahawks vs. San Francisco 49ers, August 22, 1981 (Box 7)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Oakland Raiders, August 29, 1981 (Box 7)
    - Chicago Bears vs. San Francisco 49ers, September 13, 1981 (Box 7)
    - New Orleans Saints vs. San Francisco 49ers, September 27, 1981 (Box 7)
    - Denver Broncos vs. Oakland Raiders, October 4, 1981(2 copies) (Box 7)
    - Dallas Cowboys vs. San Francisco 49ers, October 11, 1981 (Box 7)
    - Cleveland Browns vs. San Francisco 49ers, November 15, 1981 (2 copies) (Box 7)
    - New York Giants vs. San Francisco 49ers, November 29, 1981 (Box 7)
  - GameDay: an official PRO! Publication of the NFL
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Oakland Raiders, August 14, 1982 (Box 7)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. St. Louis Cardinals, August 21, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Oakland Raiders vs. San Francisco 49ers, September 12, 1982 (2 copies) (Box 7)
    - Los Angeles Raiders vs. San Diego Chargers, November 22, 1982 (Box 7)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. New Orleans Saints, November 28, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Los Angeles Raiders vs. Seattle Seahawks, December 5, 1982 (Box 7)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. San Diego Chargers, December 11, 1982 (4 copies) (Box 7)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Atlanta Falcons, December 19, 1982 (4 copies) (Box 7)
    - Los Angeles Raiders vs. Denver Broncos, December 26, 1982 (Box 7)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Los Angeles Rams, January 2, 1983 (4 copies) (Box 7)
  - World Football League Programs
    - Memphis Southmen vs. Detroit Wheels, July 10, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Chicago Fire vs. Houston Texans, July 10, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Jacksonville Sharks vs. New York Stars, July 11, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Detroit Wheels vs. Florida Blazers, July 17, 1974 (2 copies) (Box 8)
    - New York Stars vs. Birmingham Americans, July 17, 1974 (2 copies) (Box 8)
    - Honolulu Hawaiians vs. Southern California Sun, July 17, 1974 (3 copies) (Box 8)
    - Chicago Fire vs. Jacksonville Sharks, July 17, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Houston Texans vs. Philadelphia Bell, July 17, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Detroit Wheels vs. Birmingham Americans, July 31, 1974 (Box 8)
    - New York Stars vs. Jacksonville Sharks, July 31, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Portland Storm vs. Philadelphia Bell, July 31, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Houston Texans vs. Florida Blazers, July 31, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Portland Storm vs. Houston Texans, August 7, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Chicago Fire vs. Florida Blazers, August 7, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Honolulu Hawaiians vs. Jacksonville Sharks, August 8, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Detroit Wheels vs. Memphis Southmen, August 14, 1974 (2 copies) (Box 8)
    - New York Stars vs. Portland Storm, August 14, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Chicago Fire vs. Philadelphia Bell, August 14, 1974 (Box 8)
    - New York Stars vs. Houston Texans, August 21, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Southern California Sun vs. Philadelphia Bell, August 21, 1974 (2 copies) (Box 8)
    - Honolulu Hawaiians vs. Jacksonville Sharks, August 25, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Chicago Fire vs. Birmingham Americans, August 29, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Honolulu Hawaiians vs. Houston Texans, September 1, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Detroit Wheels vs. Portland Storm, September 2, 1974 (Box 8)
    - New York Stars vs. Philadelphia Bell, September 2, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Southern California Sun vs. Detroit Wheels, September 6, 1974 (Box 8)
    - New York Stars vs. Florida Blazers, September 6, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Southern California Sun vs. Chicago Fire, September 11, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Portland Storm vs. New York Stars, September 11, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Honolulu Hawaiians vs. New York Stars, September 18, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Memphis Southmen vs. Chicago Fire, September 18, 1974 (Box 8)
    - New York Stars vs. Detroit Wheels, September 24, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Honolulu Hawaiians vs. Philadelphia Bell, September 25, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Shreveport Steamer vs. Memphis Southmen, September 25, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Portland Storm vs. Birmingham Americans, September 25, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Honolulu Hawaiians vs. Birmingham Americans, October 2, 1974 (2 copies) (Box 8)
    - Portland Storm vs. Southern California Sun, October 2, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Chicago Fire vs. New York Stars, October 3, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Florida Blazers vs. Chicago Fire, October 9, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Honolulu Hawaiians vs. Birmingham Americans, October 16, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Portland Storm vs. Honolulu Hawaiians, October 16, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Memphis Southmen vs. Florida Blazers, October 16, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Honolulu Hawaiians vs. Chicago Fire, October 23, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Honolulu Hawaiians vs. Memphis Southmen, October 30, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Charlotte Hornets vs. Southern California Sun, October 31, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Shreveport Steamer vs. Charlotte Hornets, November 6, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Honolulu Hawaiians vs. Southern California Sun, November 6, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Memphis Southmen vs. Chicago Fire, November 7, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Honolulu Hawaiians vs. Portland Storm, November 13, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Southern California Sun vs. San Antonio Wings, July 5, 1975 (Box 8)
    - Honolulu Hawaiians vs. Charlotte Hornets, July 12, 1975 (Box 8)
    - Southern California Sun vs. Memphis Southmen, July 14, 1975 (Box 8)
    - Southern California Sun vs. Portland Thunder, August 3, 1975 (Box 8)
    - Honolulu Hawaiians vs. Southern California Sun, August 16, 1975 (Box 8)
    - Honolulu Hawaiians vs. Chicago Winds, August 23, 1975 (Box 8)
    - Southern California Sun vs. Philadelphia Bell, August 29, 1975 (Box 8)
    - Southern California Sun vs. Charlotte Hornets, September 14, 1975 (Box 8)
    - Southern California Sun vs. Shreveport Steamer, October 12, 1975 (Box 8)
  - USFL KICKOFF Magazine
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Birmingham Stallions, March 13, 1983 (2 copies) (Box 8)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Philadelphia Stars, April 16, 1983 (7 copies) (Box 8)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Arizona Wranglers, May 2, 1983 (7 copies) (Box 8)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Tampa Bay Bandits, May 8, 1983 (8 copies) (Box 8)
  - USFL KICKOFF Magazine, cont.
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Washington Federals, May 16, 1983 (8 copies) (Box 9)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Los Angeles Express, May 29, 1983 (8 copies) (Box 9)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. New Jersey Generals, June 4, 1983 (8 copies) (Box 9)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Denver Gold, June 13, 1983 (7 copies) (Box 9)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Boston Breakers, June 25, 1983 (8 copies) (Box 9)
  - The Global Cup – Minnesota Vikings vs. St. Louis Cardinals, Wembley Stadium, London, England, August 6, 1983 (Box 10)
  - GameDay: an official PRO! Publication of the NFL
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. New England Patriots, August 14, 1983 (Box 10)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Seattle Seahawks, August 27, 1983 (Box 10)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Philadelphia Eagles, September 3, 1983 (Box 10)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Atlanta Falcons, September 25, 1983 (Box 10)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Los Angeles Rams, October 9, 1983 (Box 10)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. New York Jets, October 30, 1983 (2 copies) (Box 10)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Miami Dolphins, November 6, 1983 (2 copies) (Box 10)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. New Orleans Saints, November 13, 1983 (Box 10)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Tampa Bay Buccaneers, December 4, 1983 (Box 10)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Dallas Cowboys, December 19, 1983 (2 copies) (Box 10)
    - GameDay
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Atlanta Falcons, November 23, 1986 (2 copies) (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. New York Giants, December 1, 1986 (2 copies) (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. New York Jets, December 7, 1986 (2 copies) (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Los Angeles Rams, December 9, 1986 (2 copies) (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. New Orleans Saints, November 15, 1987 (2 copies) (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Los Angeles Rams, December 27, 1987 (2 copies) (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Washington Redskins, November 21, 1988 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. St. Louis Rams, October 1, 1989 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. New York Giants, September 27, 1989 (2 copies) (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Washington Redskins, September 16, 1990 (3 copies) (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Tampa Bay Buccaneers, October 23, 1994 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Oakland Raiders, October 8, 2000 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Atlanta Falcons, September 9, 2001 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Carolina Panthers, October 7, 2001 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Miami Dolphins, December 16, 2001 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Philadelphia Eagles, December 22, 2001 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Washington Redskins, September 22, 2002 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. St. Louis Rams, October 6, 2002 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Philadelphia Eagles, November 25, 2002 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Green Bay Packers, December 15, 2002 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Oakland Raiders, August 14, 2003 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. New Orleans Saints, August 23, 2003 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Chicago Bears, September 7, 2003 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Cleveland Browns, September 21, 2003 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Detroit Lions, October 5, 2003 (2 copies) (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Tampa Bay Buccaneers, October 19, 2003 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. St. Louis Rams, November 2, 2003 (2 copies) (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Pittsburgh Steelers, November 17, 2003 (2 copies) (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Arizona Cardinals December 7, 2003 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Seattle Seahawks, December 27, 2003 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. St. Louis Rams, October 3, 2004 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Tampa Bay Buccaneers, October 30, 2005 (2 copies) (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. New York Giants, November 6, 2005 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Seattle Seahawks, November 20, 2005 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Arizona Cardinals, December 4, 2005 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Houston Texans, January 1, 2006 (Box 12)
      - San Francisco 49ers vs. Arizona Cardinals, September 10, 2007 (Box 12)
  - USFL KICKOFF Magazine
    - Oakland Invaders vs. New Orleans Breakers, March 4, 1984 (4 copies) (Box 10)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Los Angeles Express, March 11, 1984 (3 copies) (Box 10)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Houston Gamblers, April 16, 1984 (2 copies) (Box 10)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Washington Federals, April 22, 1984 (3 copies) (Box 10)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Denver Gold, May 5, 1984 (3 copies) (Box 10)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Arizona Wranglers May 13, 1984 (3 copies) (Box 10)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Memphis Showboats, May 19, 1984 (3 copies) (Box 10)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Jacksonville Bulls, June 2, 1984 (3 copies) (Box 10)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Michigan Panthers, June 9, 1984 (3 copies) (Box 10)
  - Official Souvenir Program